 var quest = [
   
    {
        question: "Which bird has the largest wingspan of any living bird?",
        answer:"The wandering albatross.",
    },
   
    {
        question:"Which is a non- poisonous snake?",
        answer: "python",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What type of animal is a Mexican hairless?",
        answer: "dog",
    },

    {
        question: "What kind of creature is a Portuguese man o' war?",
        answer: "jellyfish",
    },
   
    {
        question: "How animal has 10 legs?",
        answer: "lobster",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What type of animal is a Flemish giant?",
        answer: "rabbit",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Which creatures produce gossamer?",
        answer: "Spiders",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What is a palmiped?",
        answer: "Any bird with webbed feet",
    },
   
    {
        question: "From which animal is mohair obtained?",
        answer: "The angora goat",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What fish live near the bottom of the sea?",
        answer: "dermersal",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What animal has 5 arms?",
        answer: "starfish",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Which large mammal's tail is so strong it can stand on it and lift its hind legs off the ground?",
        answer: "The kangaroo",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What is a cabbage white?",
        answer: "butterfly",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What type of animal has natural habitat in or among trees?", 
        answer: "arboreal",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What animal has a trunk with the scientific name 'Proboscis?'", 
        answer: "elephant",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Which ape gets its name from the Malay word meaning 'man of the forest'?",
        answer: "orangutan",
    },
   
    {
        question: "How is the domestic cavy better known?",
        answer: "guinea pig",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What is a Drone that is the only members of the colony allowed to mate with the queen?",
        answer: "honey bee",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Piebald is an adjective is used to describe this animal with two different colored patches, usually black and white?",
        answer: "Horse",
    },
   
    {
        question: "Which is the largest mammal in the world?",
        answer: "blue whale",
    },
   
    {
        question: "This animal has two humps on (HUMP-DAY).",
        answer: "bactrian camel",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What type of animal is a basenji?",
        answer: "hunting dog",
    },
   
    {    
        question: "Which is the largest living bird?",
        answer: "ostrich",
    },
   
    {
        question: "What kind of animal is a karakul?",
        answer: "sheep",
    },
   
    {
        question: '"Murder" is the collective noun for a group of which bird?',
        answer: "crows",
    },
 ]
